Guide to the Stephen Vincent Benét and Rosemary Benét Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Family Correspondence, 1829-1962; Series II; 6.05; 15 boxes
  - General Correspondence
    - Benét, Stephanie (daughter)
      - Benét, Laura, 1934 January (Box 41, Folder 1579)
      - Benét, Rosemary, undated (Box 41, Folder 1580)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1938, undated (Box 41, Folder 1581)
    - Benét, Stephen Vincent
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1908–1916 (Box 41, Folder 1582-1583)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1916–1927 (Box 42, Folder 1584-1594)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1927–1938 (Box 43, Folder 1595-1605)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1938-1939, undated (Box 44, Folder 1606-1610)
      - Benét, James Walker, 1905-1927, undated (Box 44, Folder 1611-1613)
      - Benét, Laura, 1906-1942, undated (Box 44, Folder 1614-1616)
      - Benét, Laurence Vincent, undated (Box 44, Folder 1617)
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1920–1921 (Box 44, Folder 1618-1619)
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1920-1942, undated (Box 45, Folder 1620-1632)
      - Benét, Rosemary, undated (Box 46, Folder 1633-1643)
      - Benét, Stephanie, 1930 January 10 (Box 46, Folder 1644)
      - [Benét?], Teresa [Frances Thompson?], undated (Box 46, Folder 1645)
      - Benét, Thomas C., 1928, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 1646)
      - Benét children, undated (Box 46, Folder 1647)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1909 May 15 (Box 46, Folder 1648)
      - Carr, Rachel H.; Carr, Thomas, 1921-1935, undated (Box 46, Folder 1649-1650)
      - Mahon, Agnes I. (aunt), 1915 August 16 (Box 46, Folder 1651)
      - Rose, Elizabeth Neill (aunt), 1906, 1908 (Box 46, Folder 1652)
      - Rose, M. L., 1906-1917, undated (Box 47, Folder 1653-1654)
      - "Mont", 1907 December 31 (Box 47, Folder 1655)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 47, Folder 1656)
    - Benét, Thomas C. (son)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1938 December 22 (Box 47, Folder 1657)
      - Benét, Laura, 1934 January 7 (Box 47, Folder 1658)
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1944–1958 (Box 47, Folder 1659)
      - Clippings removed from Benét, Rosemary, 1953, undated (Box 123 (Oversize), Folder 3117)
    - Benét, William Rose (brother)
      - Benét, Laurence Vincent, 1928 May 18 (Box 47, Folder 1660)
      - Benét, Margaret Cox, 1935 November 17 (Box 47, Folder 1661)
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1921-1950, undated (Box 47, Folder 1662-1665)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1916-1943, undated (Box 47, Folder 1666-1671)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, undated (Box 48, Folder 1672-1673)
    - Carr, Rachel H. (mother-in-law)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1928 May 30 (Box 48, Folder 1674)
      - Benét, Rosemary, [1931?] March 21 (Box 48, Folder 1675)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1921-1943, undated (Box 48, Folder 1676-1677)
      - Carr, Thomas, 1920 (Box 48, Folder 1678)
    - Carr, Rosa
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1930 August 11 (Box 48, Folder 1679)
    - Carr, Thomas (father-in-law)
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1904–1922 (Box 48, Folder 1680)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1911 April 16 (Box 48, Folder 1681)
      - Carr, Rachel H., 1891–1908 (Box 48, Folder 1682)
      - Carr, Rosa, 1886 (Box 48, Folder 1683)
      - Others, 1913, undated (Box 48, Folder 1684)
    - Carr, William J.
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1936 April 1 (Box 48, Folder 1685)
    - Dawson, Rosemary Benét
      - Benét, Laura, undated (Box 48, Folder 1686)
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1936-1958, undated (Box 48, Folder 1687)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, undated (Box 48, Folder 1688)
    - Fry, Kathleen Benét (niece)
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1936-1958, undated (Box 48, Folder 1689)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, undated (Box 48, Folder 1690)
    - McVey, Harold
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1930–1938 (Box 48, Folder 1691)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1939 November 16 (Box 48, Folder 1692)
    - McVey, Harold H., Jr.
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1941–1946 (Box 48, Folder 1693)
    - McVey, Janet
      - [Carr?], Rachel H., 189[?] (Box 48, Folder 1694)
    - McVey, Margaret
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1910-1962, undated (Box 48, Folder 1695)
    - Mahon, Agnes I. (aunt)
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1925 November 3 (Box 48, Folder 1696)
    - Norris, Charles Gilman; Norris, Kathleen
      - Benét, Frances Rose, undated (Box 48, Folder 1697)
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1923-1958, undated (Box 48, Folder 1698)
      - Benét, Steven Vincent, 1916-1940, undated (Box 48, Folder 1699)
    - [Rose, M. L.] (grandmother)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1907 October 8 (Box 48, Folder 1700)
    - [Rose?], Mary Lee (cousin)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, undated (Box 48, Folder 1701)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 48, Folder 1702)
    - Rose, William J.
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1933 November 8 (Box 48, Folder 1703)
    - Sullivan, Herbert Hilary
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1919-1920, undated (Box 48, Folder 1704)
    - Wylie, Elinor (sister-in-law)
      - Benét, Rosemary, undated (Box 48, Folder 1705-1706)
      - Benét "children", undated (Box 48, Folder 1707)
  - Other Family Letters
    - Crozier, [?] to Frances Rose Benét, 1929 January 28 (Box 48, Folder 1708)
    - Curtis, Randall, Mrs. to Stephanie Benét, 1943 March 14 (Box 48, Folder 1709)
    - Day, Wendy to Rachel Benét, 1943 March 16 (Box 48, Folder 1710)
    - Doubleday, Doran Company to Laura Benét, 1928 August 17 (Box 48, Folder 1711)
    - "Fechet" to [Frances Rose Benét?], 1939 March 30 (Box 48, Folder 1712)
    - Hamill, Elizabeth to "Mary", 1829 April 30 (Box 48, Folder 1713)
    - Hatch, Norman L. to Thomas C. Benét, 1943 March 16 (Box 48, Folder 1714)
    - Hitchcock Military Academy to Frances Rose Benét, 1910–1911 (Box 48, Folder 1715)
    - Janesville (Wis.) Board of Education to Rosemary Benét, [?] February 13 (Box 48, Folder 1716)
    - Levy, D[avid?] to Peter Benét, 1845 February 22 (Box 48, Folder 1717)
    - St. Johns County Archive to Laurence Vincent Benét, 1941 August (Box 48, Folder 1718)
    - [Tucheus?], Maria to Rosemary Benét, 1947–1952 (Box 48, Folder 1719)
    - Van Hoosen, Bertha to Rachel H. Carr, undated (Box 48, Folder 1720)
    - Yale University Press to Frances Rose Benét, 1921 February 1 (Box 48, Folder 1721)
    - Yale University Press to Laura Benét, 1958 October 7 (Box 48, Folder 1722)
    - "Annie" to Stephen Vincent Benét, undated (Box 48, Folder 1723)
    - "Annie" to "Walker", 1927 February 9 (Box 48, Folder 1724)
    - "Catharine" to Rosemary Benét, [?] July 16 (Box 48, Folder 1725)
    - "Elinor" to Stephen Vincent Benét, 1937 November 13 (Box 48, Folder 1726)
    - "Emily" to Rosemary Benét, undated (Box 48, Folder 1727)
    - "Lizzie" to "Jack", undated (Box 48, Folder 1728)
    - "Mont" to Stephen Vincent Benét, 1934 June 4 (Box 48, Folder 1729)
    - "Sophie" to Rosemary Benét, 1924, 1933 (Box 49, Folder 1730)
    - Unidentified to Laura Benét, 1890, 1915 (Box 49, Folder 1731)
    - Unidentified to Stephen Vincent Benét, undated (Box 49, Folder 1732)
    - Unidentified to "Bobby", 1910, undated (Box 49, Folder 1733)
    - Unidentified, 1933, undated (Box 49, Folder 1734)
    - Various to Frances Rose Benét, 1899-1939, undated (Box 49, Folder 1735)
    - Various to Laurence Vincent Benét, 1934-1940, undated (Box 49, Folder 1736)
    - Various to S. V. (Stephen Vincent) Benét on "promotion to Chief of Ordnance", 1874 (Box 49, Folder 1737)
    - Various to S. V. (Stephen Vincent) Benét on "his retirement", 1890-1891, undated (Box 49, Folder 1738)
    - Various to S. V. (Stephen Vincent) Benét, 1845–1887 (Box 49, Folder 1739)
    - Various to Rachel H. Carr, 1903-1933, undated (Box 49, Folder 1740)
    - Various to Thomas Carr, 1884-1930, undated (Box 49, Folder 1741)
    - Empty envelopes, 1911, undated (Box 49, Folder 1742)
- Writings, 1870-1962; 1909-1944; Series III; 16.94; 29 boxes
  Organized into five subseries: Writings of Stephen Vincent Benét, Adaptations of Work by Stephen Vincent Benét, Writings of Rosemary Benét, Adaptations of Work by Rosemary Benét, and Writings of Others.
  Series III. Writings includes manuscript writings of Stephen Vincent Benét, manuscript and printed works by Rosemary Benét, adaptations of work by Stephen Vincent and Rosemary Benét, and writings by others. Printed versions of writings by Stephen Vincent Benét are filed in Series IV.
  The manuscripts of Stephen Vincent Benét consist chiefly of drafts and proofs of individual works. Source and research material, notes, outlines, and production-related material, such as jacket copy and book jackets, can also be found. Corrected and multiple drafts, revealing the evolution of particular texts, are common for many titles.
  Benét is well known for his long poem, John Brown's Body (1928), about the American Civil War, for which he was awarded a Pulitzer Prize in 1929, and for the short story, "The Devil and Daniel Webster" (1936), for which he was awarded the O. Henry Memorial Award for best American short story in 1937. Material can be found for these two popular works, as well as for longer works and collections, such as James Shore's Daughter (1934), Selected Works (1942), and the posthumous Western Star (1943). In addition to poetry and short stories, Benét also wrote book reviews, essays, forewords and introductions, radio plays, screenplays, and speeches.
  Writings of Rosemary Benét include drafts and printed versions of poems, book reviews, essays, reader reports, and short stories.
  - Writings of Stephen Vincent Benét
    - "1936"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon and autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 50, Folder 1743)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 50, Folder 1744)
    - "Abraham Lincoln"
      - Draft, motion picture scenario, typescript carbon, 1930 January 13 (Box 50, Folder 1745)
    - Abraham Lincoln: The War Years by Carl Sandburg
      - Draft, review, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 50, Folder 1746)
      - Draft, typescript carbon, circa 1939 (Box 50, Folder 1747)
    - "Ake"
      - Draft, reader report, typescript, undated (Box 50, Folder 1748)
    - "Alberich's Song"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 50, Folder 1749)
    - [All Around the Town]
      - Draft, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 50, Folder 1750)
    - "All the Dirt on Me and My Sex Life: A Superconfession"
      - Draft, story, typescript, undated (Box 50, Folder 1751)
    - "All Night Long"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 50, Folder 1752)
    - "All Souls"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 50, Folder 1753)
    - "Almayer's Folly"
      - Draft, story, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 50, Folder 1754)
    - "The Amateur of Crime"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 50, Folder 1755)
    - America
      - Draft of first page, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 50, Folder 1756)
      - Draft, typescript mimeograph, undated (Box 50, Folder 1757)
      - Galley proof, with proofreaders' marks, 1944 (Box 124 (Oversize), Folder 3118)
      - Page proof, 1944 March 17 (Box 124 (Oversize), Folder 3119)
      - Jacket copy, typescript carbon, 1944 March 24 (Box 50, Folder 1758)
    - "America, 1941"
      - Draft, review, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 50, Folder 1759)
    - "American Guide Series"
      - Draft, review, typescript carbon, undated (Box 50, Folder 1760)
    - American Memory by Henry Beston
      - Draft, review, typescript carbon, circa 1937 (Box 50, Folder 1761)
    - "Among Those Present"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 50, Folder 1762)
    - "Ancient's Song"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 50, Folder 1763)
    - "Annotated Edition"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 50, Folder 1764)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 50, Folder 1765)
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 50, Folder 1766)
    - "April Folly"
      - Draft, story, typescript, undated (Box 50, Folder 1767)
    - "Architects"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 50, Folder 1768)
      - Proof, undated (Box 50, Folder 1769)
    - "The Architecture of the Novel"
      - Draft, address, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 50, Folder 1770)
    - "As a Dream Might Flatter"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 50, Folder 1771)
    - "The Assize of God"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, corrected and signed, undated (Box 50, Folder 1772)
    - "Autumn Elegy"
      - Drafy, poem (incomplete?), autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 50, Folder 1773)
    - "Bad Dream"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 50, Folder 1774)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 50, Folder 1775)
    - "The Ballad of Harrigan"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 50, Folder 1776)
    - "The Ballad of William Sycamore"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 50, Folder 1777)
    - "Barbary Coast"
      - Outline of scenario for motion picture, typescript, undated (Box 50, Folder 1778)
    - The Barefoot Saint
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, and typescript carbon, signed, undated (Box 50, Folder 1779-1780)
      - Draft, typescript, undated (Box 50, Folder 1781)
    - The Beginning of Wisdom
      - Deleted pages, typescript and typescript carbon, undated (Box 50, Folder 1782)
    - The Best British Short Stories of 1939
      - Draft, review, typescript carbon, circa 1939 (Box 50, Folder 1783)
    - The Bishop's Beggar
      - Note, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 50, Folder 1784)
      - Draft, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 50, Folder 1785)
      - Draft, typescript and typescript carbon, undated (Box 51, Folder 1786-1787)
      - Galley proof, corrected, [1941?] (Box 124 (Oversize), Folder 3120)
    - "Black Kitten and White Kitten"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, signed, undated (Box 51, Folder 1788)
    - "The Blood of the Martyrs"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 51, Folder 1789)
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 51, Folder 1790)
    - "Blossom and Fruit"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 51, Folder 1791)
    - A Book of Americans
      - Draft, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 51, Folder 1792)
      - Draft, autograph manuscript, corrected, circa 1933 (Box 51, Folder 1793)
      - Draft fragments by Rosemary Carr, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 51, Folder 1794)
      - Draft, typescript and typescript carbon (incomplete), corrected, undated (Box 51, Folder 1795)
      - Page proofs, circa 1933 (Box 51, Folder 1796-1797)
      - "Quotes" for [publicity?], typescript, undated (Box 51, Folder 1798)
    - "Broadcast Between T. S. Stribling and Stephen Vincent Benet"
      - Draft, [interview?], typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 51, Folder 1799)
    - The Burning City
      - Draft pages, "some dropped out," autograph manuscript and typescript, corrected, undated (Box 52, Folder 1800)
      - Galley proof, circa 1936 (Box 124 (Oversize), Folder 3121)
    - "By the Waters of Babylon"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 52, Folder 1801)
    - "Californiay ('49)"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 52, Folder 1802)
    - "Cardinal Myers Elected Pope"
      - Draft, sketch, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 52, Folder 1803)
    - "Carl Sandburg"
      - Draft, essay, typescript carbon, undated (Box 52, Folder 1804)
    - "The Changeling"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, 1941 February 17 (Box 52, Folder 1805)
    - "Chant for United Nations"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 52, Folder 1806)
    - "A Cheerful Song"
      - Drafts, poem, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 52, Folder 1807)
    - Cheers for Miss Bishop
      - Draft pages, screen treatment, typescript and typescript carbon, corrected, 1939, undated (Box 52, Folder 1808-1809)
      - Draft, screen treatment, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 52, Folder 1810-1811)
      - Draft, screenplay, "re-write by Adelaide Heilbron," typescript mimeograph, 1940 August 16 (Box 52, Folder 1812)
    - "Chemical Analysis"
      - Draft, poem, typescript (2 copies), undated (Box 52, Folder 1813)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 52, Folder 1814)
    - "Chicago"
      - Draft, address, typescript, undated (Box 53, Folder 1815)
    - "A Child Is Born"
      - Draft, radio play, typescript mimeograph, 1942 December 4 (Box 53, Folder 1816-1819)
    - "Christmas--1925"
      - Draft, poem, autograph manuscript, 1925 (Box 53, Folder 1820)
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, 1925 (Box 53, Folder 1821)
    - The Christmas Companion
      - Review, typescript carbon, corrected, [1939] (Box 53, Folder 1822)
    - "Cockcrow"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 53, Folder 1823)
    - "Complaint of Body, the Ass, Against His Rider, the Soul"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, corrected (3 copies), undated (Box 53, Folder 1824)
    - "A Creed for Americans"
      - Draft, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 53, Folder 1825)
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 53, Folder 1826)
      - Draft, typescript carbon, undated (Box 53, Folder 1827)
    - "The Crime of Professor Sandwich"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 53, Folder 1828)
    - "The Curfew Tolls"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 53, Folder 1829)
    - "The Curst Kitchen"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 53, Folder 1830)
    - "The Danger of Shadows"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 53, Folder 1831)
    - "Daniel Webster"
      - Draft, [essay?], typescript, undated (Box 53, Folder 1832)
    - "Days Pass: Men Pass"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 53, Folder 1833)
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, with autograph manuscript notes on verso, undated (Box 53, Folder 1834)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 53, Folder 1835)
    - Dear Adolf
      - Source material, 1941-1942, undated (Box 53, Folder 1836-1839)
      - Draft removed from Source material, undated (Box 124 (Oversize), Folder 3122)
      - Source material, 1941-1942, undated (Box 54, Folder 1840-1842)
      - Clipping removed from Source material, 1942 March 5 (Box 124 (Oversize), Folder 3123)
      - Draft pages, radio plays, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 54, Folder 1843)
      - Drafts, radio plays, typescript and typescript carbon, undated (Box 54, Folder 1844)
      - Drafts, radio plays, typescript carbon, corrected, 1942 (Box 54, Folder 1845)
      - Drafts, radio plays, typescript mimeograph, corrected, annotated, and signed, 1942 (Box 54, Folder 1846-1847)
      - Radio plays, typescript mimeograph, 1942 (Box 54, Folder 1848)
      - Miscellaneous pages, typescript mimeograph, 1942 (Box 54, Folder 1849)
      - Publicity, 1942 (Box 54, Folder 1850)
    - "A Death in the Country"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 54, Folder 1851)
    - "The Death of Pretty Boy Floyd"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 54, Folder 1852)
    - "Dedication"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 54, Folder 1853)
    - "A Defense of Mrs. Anonymous"
      - Draft, essay, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 54, Folder 1854)
    - The Devil and Daniel Webster
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 54, Folder 1855)
      - Page proof (incomplete), 1937 (Box 54, Folder 1856)
      - Draft, opera, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 55, Folder 1857)
      - Draft, opera, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 55, Folder 1858)
      - Draft, outline for treatment, typescript carbon, 1940 October 25 (Box 55, Folder 1859)
      - Drafts, treatment (incomplete), typescript and typescript carbon, 1940–1941 (Box 55, Folder 1860)
      - Draft, treatment, typescript carbon, undated (Box 55, Folder 1861)
      - Draft, treatment, typescript carbon, undated (Box 55, Folder 1862)
      - Draft, screenplay, "Final Script," typescript mimeograph, 1941 February 18 (Box 55, Folder 1863)
    - "The Die-Hard"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 55, Folder 1864)
    - "Difference"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 55, Folder 1865)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 55, Folder 1866)
    - "Do You Remember Springfield?"
      - Draft, poem, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 55, Folder 1867)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 55, Folder 1868)
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, corrected (3 copies), undated (Box 55, Folder 1869)
    - "Doc Melhorn and the Pearly Gates"
      - Draft, story, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 55, Folder 1870)
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 55, Folder 1871)
    - "Dolls That Pass in the Night"
      - Draft, dramatic scenario, typescript carbon, undated (Box 55, Folder 1872)
    - "Dowry Song"
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 55, Folder 1873)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 55, Folder 1874)
    - "Early" writings
      - Drafts and printed version, 1909-1912, undated (Box 55, Folder 1875)
    - "The Educated Pig"
      - Galley proof, story, 1930 August 4 (Box 124 (Oversize), Folder 3124)
      - Page proof, 1930 August 8 (Box 124 (Oversize), Folder 3125)
    - "Elementals"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 55, Folder 1876)
    - "The Enemies"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, circa 1932 (Box 55, Folder 1877)
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 55, Folder 1878)
    - "Ernest Hemingway"
      - Notes, typescript, undated (Box 55, Folder 1879)
      - Draft, essay, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 55, Folder 1880)
    - "Everybody Was Very Nice"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 55, Folder 1881)
    - "Excuse It, Please!"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 55, Folder 1882)
    - "Faces of Angels"
      - Draft, poem, typescript (2 copies), undated (Box 55, Folder 1883)
    - "Family Complaint"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 55, Folder 1884)
      - Draft, poem, typescript (3 copies), undated (Box 55, Folder 1885)
    - "Famous"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 56, Folder 1886)
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon (2 copies), 1942; 1944 (Box 56, Folder 1887)
    - "Farewell Chanty--1942"
      - Draft, poem, typescript mimeograph (4 copies), [1942?] (Box 56, Folder 1888)
    - "The Fiddling Wood"
      - Draft, poem, typescript [mimoegraph?], signed, 1919 (Box 56, Folder 1889)
    - "Fire Island"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 56, Folder 1890)
    - "Fireworks"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 56, Folder 1891)
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 56, Folder 1892)
    - ["The following consists of five sketches…"]
      - Proof, inscribed, undated (Box 56, Folder 1893)
    - "Footnote from Villon"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, with autograph manuscript notes on verso, undated (Box 56, Folder 1894)
    - "For City Lovers"
      - Draft, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 56, Folder 1895)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 56, Folder 1896)
    - "For City Spring"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 56, Folder 1897)
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 56, Folder 1898)
    - "For R.C.B."
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 56, Folder 1899)
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 56, Folder 1900)
    - "For the Flyleaf of the Third Edition of 'Young Adventure'"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 56, Folder 1901)